The secret lies within.
Identity is a mystery, thriller film directed by James Mangold.
Complete strangers stranded at a remote desert motel during a raging storm
soon find themselves the target of a deranged murderer.
As their numbers thin out, the travelers begin to turn on each
other, as each tries to figure out who the killer is.
Ed, played by John Cusack.
Rhodes, played by Ray Liotta.
Paris, played by Amanda Peet.
Larry, played by John Hawkes.
Doctor, played by Alfred Molina.
Ginny, played by Clea DuVall.
Identity is a 2003 American slasher film directed by James Mangold, written by Michael Cooney, and starring
John Cusack, Ray Liotta, and Amanda Peet with Alfred Molina, Clea DuVall, and Rebecca De Mornay.
Inspired by Agatha Christie's 1939 whodunit And Then There Were None, the film follows ten strangers in an isolated
hotel, who are temporarily cut off from the rest of the world and mysteriously killed off one by one.
Several events that take place in the hours before the characters' arrival are introduced at key moments in the film using reverse chronology structure
and, in a parallel story, a murderer awaits a verdict at a crucial trial that will determine whether he will be executed for his crimes.
The film explores themes of prostitute, prisoner, psychopath, nevada, detective.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.